http://www.calbanktrust.com/privacy-and-security/

Privacy and Security | California Bank & Trust
Compare0Clear All
You can compare maximum three products at a time. Please adjust the selection accordingly.
Compare
You can only compare three products at a time. Unselect an account or use clear all to start over.
Hide
Choose Your State
Rates and products offered may differ from state to state. To see the rate and offering available to you, please select the state where you bank. (Your privacy is important to us—see our Privacy Notice)
--- Choose Your State ---
Alabama
Alaska
Arizona
Arkansas
California
Colorado
Connecticut
Money Market Account
Certificates of Deposit (CDs)
Individual Retirement Account (IRA)
Safe Deposit Box
Online and Mobile Banking
Online Banking
Mobile Banking
Mobile Deposit
Mobile Payments
Zelle
Specialized Services
Private Mortgage
Securities-Based Lending (ILOC)
Lending Solutions
Wealth Management
Wealth Planning
Investment Management
Trust Services
Insurance
Trends and insights
Educational Webinars
Search the website
What Can We Help You Find?
Login
Login
Privacy and Security
Our company privacy and security polices.
Privacy and Security
Safeguarding your financial and personal information is important in this digital age. At California Bank & Trust, we make every effort to help protect your data, in-branch and online. Review our company policies and articles on fraud protection to find out more.
Privacy Notice
Learn how California Bank & Trust handles your personal information.
Learn More
Mobile Banking App Privacy Policy
Learn how California Bank & Trust handles your personal information in our mobile banking app.
Learn More
Online Privacy Statement
California Bank & Trust’s online privacy statement.
Learn More
Amazing Deals Mobile App Privacy Policy
Describes the types of information California Bank & Trust collects through the AmaZing Deals mobile application and what we do with that information.
Learn More
Treasury Management Mobile App Privacy Policy
California Bank & Trust’s Treasury Management Mobile App Privacy Policy.
Learn More
Positive Pay Mobile Privacy Policy
Describes the types of information California Bank & Trust collects through the positive pay mobile app and what we do with this information.
Learn More
Got a question?
We've got the answer right here.
Visit FAQs
Talk to a banker today.
Contact us to get quick answers at (800) 355-0507 or a branch near you.
Receive tips and quarterly updates to help your business succeed.
California Bank & Trust, a division of Zions Bancorporation, N.A. Member FDIC
Equal Housing Lender | NMLS #467014
© 2020 Zions Bancorporation, N.A. All rights reserved.
